Hi Katherine.
Selam Katherine.
&gt;&gt; Hi Kunal.
&gt;&gt; Selam Kunal.
&gt;&gt; How are you feeling?
&gt;&gt; Nasıl hissediyorsun?
&gt;&gt; I'm feeling a little tired.
&gt;&gt; Biraz yorgun hissediyorum.
How about you?
Ya sen?
&gt;&gt; Me too, me too.
&gt;&gt; Ben de, ben de.
I suspect that some of our students are perhaps feeling the same way.
Sanıyorum bazı öğrencilerimiz de aynı şekilde hissediyor olabilir.
&gt;&gt; Probably. &gt;&gt; And that's okay.
&gt;&gt; Muhtemelen. &gt;&gt; Ve bu sorun değil.
It's a really long lesson too.
Gerçekten çok uzun bir ders.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, it is. &gt;&gt; And this is a great point for
&gt;&gt; Evet, öyle.
walk away from the computer.
bilgisayardan uzaklaşmaları için harika bir nokta.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, and while you're doing that you could actually
&gt;&gt; Evet, ve bunu yaparken birilerine
also show someone the app you've made so far.
şu ana kadar yaptığın uygulamayı da gösterebilirsin.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, talk to your friend about the new ideas that you have learned
&gt;&gt; Evet, arkadaşlarınla Android dünyasında öğrendiğin
in the Android world and come back and
yeni fikirler hakkında konuş ve geri dön ve konuşmalarını
share that conversation with us on the discussion forum.
tartışma forumunda bizimle paylaş.
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Evet.